[{
  "id": 1,
  "question": "How would you display a list of Employees on a webpage along with where they were in the list?",
  "a": "Loop through and print the index",
  "b": "Loop through and print the employees",
  "c": "Loop through and print the index and the employee",
  "d": "Pass both the index and the employee to a web service",
  "answer": "c"
},
{
  "id": 2,
  "question": "Where would you put it?",
  "a": "In the Component",
  "b": "In the Template",
  "c": "In the Injectable decorator",
  "d": "In the module",
  "answer": "c"
},
{
  "id": 3,
  "question": "Angular Js is based on",
  "a": "MVC Architecture",
  "b": "Decorator pattern",
  "c": "MVVM Architectural pattern",
  "d": "Observer Pattern",
  "answer": "c"
},
{
  "id": 4,
  "question": "AngularJS expressions are written using",
  "a": "(expression)",
  "b": "{{expression}}",
  "c": "{{{expression}}}",
  "d": "[expression]",
  "answer": "b"
},
{
  "id": 5,
  "question": "Which directive initializes an AngularJS application?",
  "a": "ng-init",
  "b": "ng-app",
  "c": "ngSrc",
  "d": "ng-start",
  "answer": "b"
},
{
  "id": 6,
  "question": "Which of following is not valid AngularJs Filter",
  "a": "lowercase",
  "b": "orderby",
  "c": "currency",
  "d": "email",
  "answer": "d"
},
{
  "id": 7,
  "question": "How do you share data between controller and view?",
  "a": " using Model",
  "b": " using services",
  "c":"using factory",
  "d":"using $scope",
 
  "answer": "b"
},{
  "id": 8,
  "question": "The . . . . . decorator allows us to define the pipe name that is globally available for use in any template in the across application.",
  "a": "pipeName",
  "b": "pipeDeco",
  "c": "Pipe",
  "d": "none",
  "answer": "c"
},
{
  "id": 9,
  "question": "Observables help you manage . . . . . . . . data.",
  "a": "synchronous",
  "b": "asynchronous",
  "c": "Both asynchronous & synchronous",
  "d": "None of above",
  "answer": "b"
},
{
  "id": 10,
  "question": "Which of following is not valid AngularJs Filter",
  "a": "lowercase",
  "b": "orderby",
  "c": "currency",
  "d": "email",
  "answer": "d"
}
]